Official uniform style.
Prefect of Yunzhou,
Gu Wenyuan.
The corpse doesn't decay.
The jade marrow has a spirit.
Lin Yan,
do you know Prefect Gu?
I...
When I saw this face,
my heart suddenly ached.
It seems
like I know him.
But I can't remember.
This mark
has been here for 7 years.
But I don't remember how I got it.
This room is sealed.
It is only connected
to the outside through the underwater passage.
Gu Wenyuan passed away here in meditation,
there must be a deep meaning.
Let's search carefully
to see if there are other clues.
Miss Xiaocui,
do you happen to know this place?
I exhausted my efforts in mystical arts
and obtained the fragments of the Nine Turns Reincarnation.
Only then did I know that in this world,
there's an evil method of seizing bodies to extend life.
It's too late to regret.
Prefect Gu,
I am Shen Mo,
son of Shen Qingshan from the Criminal Investigation Department.
I've tracked a bizarre case here.
I hope the Prefect's spirit in heaven
can help me uncover the truth
to comfort the dead.
The material is the same,
but the degree of nourishment is different.
The one at the morgue had thin blood veins.
This one
feels warm like holding warm jade.
The blood veins have formed a net.
It seems
it has been nourished for a long time.
There are very fine cracks inside.
At the cracks,
there seem to be shadows flowing.
Latecomers.
I am Gu Wenyuan.
My daughter Zijin is not dead.
I used the Turtle Breath Pill and the Soul Sealing Talisman
to make her feign death,
and hid her in the ice coffin on the lower level.
But I am exhausted.
The evil array has been set.
Qin Muzhi conspired with a noble in the palace
to use the array
to alter the nation's destiny
and extend their lives.
Be careful.
Qin Muzhi is not the mastermind.
There is a mastermind behind him.
Qintian...
The remnant soul is bound.
This array is still running.
There's an ice cellar below.
Gu Zijin should be in it.
My lord.
Beware of traps.
Gu Wenyuan's remnant soul is bound.
What he said shouldn't be false.
Seven years.
The body is still so well-preserved.
The complexion looks alive.
The coffin is made of special cold jade,
which can keep the body from decaying.
What an exquisite technique,
and so dangerous.
This talisman.
It's not just soul sealing.
It also draws souls and gathers spirits.
She is being nourished as a vessel.
Once the array is activated,
another's soul will be forcibly injected into her body,
to replace her.
There is a mastermind behind Qin Muzhi,
and it involves the Qintian.
Could it be the Qintian Directorate?
Who are you?
Where is my father?
Miss Gu,
I am Shen Mo, Registrar of the Penal Bureau.
Your father, Prefect Gu Wenyuan,
has already passed away in meditation outside.
We found you here,
sleeping.
Sleeping...
Father said
he would take me to a safe place
to wait for his return.
My head hurts. So many voices.
He said my father would be resurrected,
and we would be reunited.
Miss Gu,
is there a spell on your left arm?
Do you remember
who drew it for you?
You are here to stop my father from resurrecting.
You are enemies!
You've been placed under a Soul Control Contract or a similar spell.
Your memories have been tampered with.
Miss Gu,
wake up!
Prefect Gu has passed away.
He wanted you to live,
not become a vessel for another's soul.
Lies!
Father will definitely return!
Miss Gu,
listen to me.
Seven years ago, your father Gu Wenyuan
discovered the evil Nine Cycles Reincarnation Array,
and was murdered.
His body is in the upper stone chamber.
Think carefully.
In your memory,
is your father's promise to you
always blurry?
Is there always a voice
telling you
what to believe?
This spell is not only for control,
but also for monitoring and tracking.
The spell is temporarily suppressed.
Miss Gu,
can you remember anything now?
Lin Yan.
Brother,
is that you?
You
recognize me?
On your arm,
is there a mark?
They planted a Master Pact on me.
Brother Lin Yan.
The one on you
is a Subordinate Pact,
controlled by me.
Mr. Shen.
Before my father died,
he asked me to pass a message to Uncle Shen Qingshan,
just one sentence.
The Nine Cycles are not reincarnation,
the Dragon Vein devours souls.
On the ninth floor of the Qintian Directorate,
someone is waiting for you.
Unfortunately,
I couldn't meet Uncle Shen.
Mo'er.
That pagoda has nine stories,
but the world only knows of eight.
The ninth story,
it is said,
hides the dynasty's greatest secret.
Qintian.
This talisman
is the last thing Father gave me.
He said,
if one day I wake up
and meet someone trustworthy,
I could use this talisman to go to Baiyun Temple
and find Daoist Master Lu Mingyuan.
My Lord.
Up there,
someone is coming down the well.
Check the other end of the underwater passage.
Dive underwater,
and find another exit.
Hurry.
Send a signal.
Notify Lord Qin.
The fish are in the net.
Father,
where exactly are you?